你正被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密的系统
The government has a secret system...
有一台机器无时无刻不在监视着你
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
我知道是因为这个系统是我建的
I know,because I built it.
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动 但事实上它可以侦测任何事
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror,but it sees everything...
包括发生在平民百姓身上的暴力犯罪 像你一样的普通百姓
violent crimes involving ordinary people,people like you,
在政府看来无关紧要的暴力犯罪
Crimes the government considered irrelevant.
他们不采取行动 所以我决定我要去干预
They wouldn't act,so I decided I would.
但我需要一个搭档 某个有能力去干预的人
But I needed a partner... someone with the skills to intervene.
为了躲避当局追查 我们只能秘密行动
Hunted by the authorities,we work in secret.
你永远不会发现我们
You will never find us.
但无论你是受害者还是罪犯 只要你的号码被选中 我们一定会找到你
But victim or perpetrator,if you're number's up,we'll find you.
《疑犯追踪》 第1季 第16集
Person of Interest S01E16 720p HDTV x264
我其他的西装有什么问题?
- What's wrong with my other suits?
Reese先生 那些西装比较适合杀手 不适合这个角色
- They're fine for a hired assassin,mr. Reese,just not for this particular job.
我这是要去哪儿?
- Where am I going?
去和那些最优秀的最棒的打成一片
- To mingle with the best and brightest.
华尔街 我们有一个新任务了
Wall street. We have a new number.
Adam Saunders先生 他是个自营交易员 供职于Baylor Zimm投资银行
Mr. Adamaunders,he's a prop trader At the investment firm of baylor zimm.
- 自营交易员? - 也叫业主账户交易员
- Prop trader? - Proprietary.
他负责用银行自己的资金做投资 而不是用客户的资金
He invests the bank's own money,not the clients'.
他似乎是那种标准的 高学历 高收入的华尔街野心家
He seems to be your typical overeducated,overcompensated wall street highflier.
- 这样可以了 - 不可以
They're fine. - No.
裤脚应该正好盖住鞋帮 不能太长
The cuff should shiver on the shoe,not break.
Saunders已经和证监会有过交锋
Saunders has already had a brush with the s.E.C.,
他被怀疑在做内线交易 但无法证明
An accusation of insider trading,unproven,
所以他这样冒险 可能已经把自己置身危险中了
So his risk taking may have led him into dangerous waters.
我希望你可以接近他
I want you to get close to him.
我对华尔街那些一窍不通
- I don't know anything about wall street.
漫步华尔街― 历久弥新的成功投资策略
- Well,here a start,although it doesn't really matter.
好吧 你可以从这开始 虽然这可能派不上用场
投行里的人只是看上去聪明 衣着光鲜 而我们已经解决后者了
Banking is mostly looking clever and wearing the right clothes,and we've managed the second part.
我不知道怎么会这样 不过这家伙知道太多了
- I don't know how this works,but he's seen too much.
TRITAK  可能内线交易 目标持续监视中
TRITAK  **** SURVEILLANCE
我们会搞定的
- We'll clean it up.
不计代价 搞定他
- Whatever it takes.
我是自营交易员 不是导游
- I'm a prop trader,not a tour guide.
这可是个大客户 他给咱们带来生意 上百万的生意
- And this guy's a whale. He brings us business.It's millions.
如果我是客户经纪人 那正合胃口
- And that'd be great,if I handled clients,
但我只为Baylor Zimm做投资
But the only people i make money for are baylor and zimm.
他可不止在问我们一家投行 一定要抓住这个客户
- The amount of bank this guy's talking,it'll bleed into ours soon enough.
Sydney知道这事吗?
- Sydney know about this?
客户点名要你
- Said they requested you by name.
他们肯定觉得你业务精通
Someone must think you know what you're doing.
Paul 你这是在拍马屁让我感觉轻飘飘
- Look,you're backing me into a corner on this,paul.
我自己心里可有底呢
I've got my eye on a thing.
嘿 你以为朋友要来干嘛的?
Hey,what are friends for?
何况你都不用和那个客户碰面 只需要见他的代表 好像是资产经理
Besides,you don't even have to meet the whale,just his rep,some asset manager.
好极了 我的2天时间要交给一个 涂发蜡 穿细条纹西服的人了
- Outstanding,I'll be spending two days with hair gel and a pin -Striped suit.
实际上这是格伦格子呢的
- It's glen check,actually.
John Rooney 资产经理
John rooney,assets.
Adam Saunders 我很精通业务
- Adam saunders. I know what I'm doing.
我的客户不想透露他的名字
- My client prefers to stay anonymous.
他很... 低调
He's the...silent type.
他还不喜欢登高
- He's also not fond of heights.
Reese先生 我原以为房顶只是你的地盘
I thought rooftops were your domain,mr. Reese.
你的口碑很好
- Your reputation precedes you.
我的客户在花他自己钱投资的时候 很在乎口碑
My client trusts reputations when it comes to his money.
口碑不一定准的 他打算投资多少?
- Reputations can be deceiving. How much are we talking about?
第一笔 这只是个零头
- At first,pocket change.
我的客户喜欢赌大的
My client likes to roll the dice.
不做通胀保值债券 不做通胀挂钩债券 不做短期基金
No tips,no i-Bonds,no short-Term funds.
要做点刺激的
Play jazz.
就把这当做是个考试吧 Saunders先生
Consider it an audition,mr. Saunders.
现在已经开始了
It starts now.
你学得真快 Reese先生
you're a quick study,mr. Reese.
Adam 快过来 正在宣读判决呢
- Adam,get over here,they're reading.
我是Andrea Foxglove 我正在曼哈顿下区刑事法庭为您报道
This is andrea foxglove,reporting outside the criminal courthouse in lower manhattan.
我们收到消息说 陪审团已经准备好 宣判Robert Keller涉嫌谋杀案了
We've received word that the jury has returned in the robert keller murder trial.
这事你知道吗? Robert Keller 维尔塔南制药前任CEO
- You following this,robert keller,former ceo of virtanen pharmaceuticals?
他涉嫌谋杀 正在受审
Guy's standing trial for murder.
这个案子我很熟悉
- I'm familiar with the case.
只要他被判有罪 这家公司就破产了
- Only thing between this company and chapter 11 is an acquittal.
Saunders 你一直是悲观主义者
- Ever the pessimist,saunders.
坏事传千里
- Nothing breeds like bad news.
对股票经纪人同样适用 对吗 Vic?
Even on the broker side. Right,vic?
他们公司的股票已经抄底了
- Bad news is already priced in.
Keller的女婿现在掌控大局
Keller's son-In-Law's steering the ship.
它现在是抄底价的蓝筹股 聪明的投资已经进场了 伙计
It's a blue chip at a bargain-Basement price,smart money's already in,pal.
这就是为什么我能在这操控大额资金
That's why I get to handle the big bucks around here.
你还嫩着呢
You just went pro too early.
非常嫩
- Way too early.
她是Sydney Baylor 公司合伙人之一
- That's sydney baylor,a partner in the firm.
她也有自己的口碑
She also has a reputation.
哪方面的口碑?
- Reputation for what?
各方面
everything.
你把维尔塔南公司的股票 挂到最后一分钟 不想让我看到
- You held the sell tickets on virtanen to the last minute so I wouldn't see.
做空1亿是吗 Adam?
$100 million shorted,adam?
你说你希望这里有个扭转乾坤的人
- You said you wanted playmakers around here.
等等 你做空维尔塔南公司? 你是疯了还是傻了?
- Wait,you short sold virtanen? Are you out of your mind?
如果他背叛有罪 他们的股票一泻千里 我还是可以用挂牌的价格卖掉
- It's guilty,their stock craters,and I hold the price that I sold for.
这才叫聪明的投资 Victor
See,that's the smart money,victor.
等... 着... 瞧
Let...it...ride.
好吧 小子 不过你想清楚你用什么在赌
- All right,kid,but consider what you're betting.
消息说已经正式宣判了
I'm getting word that a verdict has just been read.
现在正在宣读
They're relaying it now.
所有罪名成立
Guilty of all charges.
随着正式宣判 地区检察官立即宣布了 指控Virtanen公司的CFO Mark Lawson的罪名
Immediately following the verdict,the d.A. Announced charges against virtanen cfo mark lawson.
恭喜你
- Congratulations.
如果你再敢那么做 你就准备去和 占领华尔街的人一起睡露天帐篷吧
You do that again,and you'll find yourself the most successful occupier down in a tent on the street.
想为维尔塔南制药 一泻千里的股票喝一杯吗?
- Feel like having a drink over the grave of virtanen pharmaceuticals?
为什么不呢?
- Why not?
我再找些人 收市钟响后 我们楼下见
- I'll round up some guys.Meet you downstairs after the closing bell.
克隆Adam Saunders的手机 失败
Adam *** FAILED
Finch 无法和他的手机配对
- His phone didn't pair,finch.
以前发生过吗?
That ever happen before?
我能想到的只有 已经有人抢先一步克隆他的手机了
- All I can think is that somebody else already blue -Jacked him.
看来不止我们在调查Adam Saunders
It appears we're not the only ones looking into adam saunders.
不奇怪
- I see why.
他一直在用别人的钱赌博 自己在一边幸灾乐祸
Guy plays poker with other people's money and gloats about it.
我不这样认为
- I wouldn't be so sure about that.
那样的人不追求胜利 他们追求这种刺激的感觉
Someone like that,the win doesn't concern him.It's the rush.
维尔塔南制药
- Virtanen.
一石二鸟 你是怎么知道的?
Two vultures,one stone. How did you know?
我什么消息都读
- I read everything,
其他那些金融公司的人可不这么干
All the 10k financials nobody else bothered to.
维尔塔南制药没有什么拳头产品要退出
Virtanen didn't have any blockbuster drugs in the pipeline.
除了家族企业 他们已经把能当的都当了 只为应付Keller的官司 CFO的就更别说了
They'd hocked everything but the family cow For keller's legal defense,not to mention the cfo's.
他们想把这些消息藏起来 不过 被我发现了 Keller只不过是冰山一角
It was all buried,but I found it,and keller was just the tip of the iceberg.
他们已经走到末路了 所以我赌了一把
That ship was going down,so I took the bet.
有风险才有收益
-  no risk,no reward.
你玩过俄罗斯轮盘赌吗?
- You ever play russian roulette?
你想玩的话 你得赌上命
You want to get in the game,you got to spin the cylinder.
你到他家了吗 Finch?
you in his apartment yet,finch?
这里的房租肯定贵得吓人
- The rent on this place must be a staggering.
说不定这也是为什么他没有什么家具
Maybe that's why he doesn't have any furniture.
Reese先生 在Sauders的衣橱里有一点小钱
Mr. Reese,there's a small fortune in saunders's closet.
没问题的话请签字
- Whenever you're ready.
作为一个在银行工作的 他好像不太信任银行
For a banker,he doesn't seem to trust banks.
200块一叠 有好几叠
Bundles of $200 each.
再来一杯苏打水
- And another club soda.
你买单 但你自己不喝酒
- You pay,but you don't drink.
我也喝 只是现在不喝
- I drink,just not right now.
Adam每次来这里都想保持思维敏捷
- Adam here prefers to keep his wits about him at all times.
我讨厌他这样
I hate that.
今天你参观得如何?
How was the dime tour?
我们这位自营交易朋友名不虚传吧?
Was our proprietary friend here worth the reputation?
名不虚传
- Every penny.
他在这呢 胜者为王先生
- There he is,mr. Big shot.
你知道我今天得向多少个客户道歉吗?
You know how many clients i had to apologize to today
尤其当他们发现 我帮他们买了你做空的股票
When they found out I put them in a stock you shorted?
好吧
- Okay.
下次 做足你的功课
Next time,do your homework.
做功课?
- Homework?
你以为我们还在小学吗?
What are we,in grade school?
噢 对不起 Vic
- Oh,sorry,vic.
我想大概你还嫩着呢
I guess you just went pro too early.
- 嘿! - 给我小心! 来呀!
- Hey! - Watch it! Come on!
噢 天啊!
- Oh,my god!
我们走吧
- Let's go.
嘿 小心我的西装!
- Hey! Watch it!My suit!
嘿 Finch 这些华尔街的交易员 白天拿上百万去赌博 晚上在酒吧斗殴
hey,finch,we've got a wall street trader That gambles millions by day,fights in bars at night,
并且有人在调查他
And someone's tracking him.
今晚你盯着他
Stay on him tonight.
如果有人要对他不利 很可能会在他家里下手
If somebody goes after him,it'll likely happen at his home.
是的 可问题是他不打算回家
- Yeah,problem is,he isn't going home.
看起来他还要加个班
Looks like he's working overtime.
Adam和他老板的关系 比我们想像的要更进一步 Finch
Adam is closer to his boss than we thought,finch.
他到底是谁?
Who is this guy?
Adam昨晚没有回家
Adam never came home last night.
反正我都在那儿了 我就顺便复印了一下他的个人资料
Since it was there,i took the liberty of copying some of his personal records.
我能解答一部分疑问了
I filled in some of the gaps,not all.
我找到了Saunders母亲的死亡证明 那年他9岁
I do have a death certificate for saunders' mother from when he was nine.
3年后 一个叫Robert Sowoski的人 签署了他的监护文件
Guardianship papers signed by a robert sowoski from three years later.
没有他父亲的资料?
- No father in the picture?
我想没有
- I guess not.
我从他的私人电脑里找到他的雇佣合同
I pulled up his employment contract from his personal computer.
是Sydney Baylor亲自雇佣他的
Sydney baylor hired him herself.
说不定是他们的私人关系 帮他平步青云 升到交易员的职位
Their private relationship may account for his speedy rise to a trading desk.
似乎没有睡出锦绣前程这么简单 Finch
- This looks like a little more than sleeping your way to the top,finch.
记录里没有别的污点
- No other smudges on his record,
只不过6个月前卷入了证监会的调查
Except for a securities and exchange commission Investigation that involved him six months ago.
我不知道原因
I don't know why.
Carter警探可以帮上忙
- Maybe detective carter could help.
再说吧
- We'll see.
我已经搞定了对Adam的监控了
Until then,I've taken care of the current surveillance on adam.
GPRS: 通用分组无线业务
After a gprs reroute,no one will be listening to his calls.
把GPRS改到发送后 没人能监听他的电话了
如果有人还想听他电话 他们就必须接近他
If someone makes another attempt on his phone,they'll have to get close.
那样就会被我们抓住
- And we'll nail them.
- Joss Carter? - 我是
- Joss carter? - Yeah.
你在西区干洗店送洗的衣服
- I have your delivery here from westside dry cleaning.
我没送洗过衣服啊
- I didn't have any dry cleaning.
这里有你的名字
- Well,got your name on it here,so--
是什么衣服?
- What is it?
一套男士西服
- One man's suit.
在这签名就好
Just sign right here.
谢谢
- Thank you.
请去世界金融中心3号
3 world financial center,please.
John 会想把西服要回来的
- John's gonna want that suit back.
Navaad先生去哪了?
So where's mr. Navaad?
我借用他车期间 他带家人去看尼克斯队的比赛了
- He's taking his family to a knicks game while I borrow his taxi.
Adam Saunders? 他有麻烦了?
- Adam saunders? Is he in trouble?
也许是的 他需要我们的帮助 Carter警探 而我需要你的帮助
- He might be.He needs our help,detective carter,and I need yours.
这就是为什么我们要去世界金融中心3号吗?
- Is that why we're going to 3 world financial center?
不 那里是证监会分区办公室
- No,that's the regional offices of the securities and exchange commission.
我们要看证监会 有关Saunders先生的密封文件
We need to get a look at sealed s.E.C. Records pertaining to mr. Saunders.
你觉得我可以办到?
And you think i can just do that?
要是有人能的话 那么就是你了
- If anyone can do it,you can.
好吧
- All right.
我试试看
I'll see what I can do.
你还开了计价器?
You turned on the meter?
别忘了给小费
- Don't forget to tip.
- 三倍浓缩的 - 没问题
- Triple espresso,please. - No problem.
三倍浓缩哦?
- Oh,triple espresso?
好多咖啡因 你一定是累了
That's a lot of caffeine. You must be tired.
我是烦了爱管闲事的证监会调查员
- I am tired of nosy s.E.C. Investigators.
你的质询6个月前就结束了
Your inquiry wrapped six months ago.
我不能让又一个你这样的 常春藤盟校毕业的小废物逃脱
- And I can't let another ivy league punk like yourself get away with it.
我还是没啥要说的
- And I still have nothing to say.
你一直很会守口如瓶
- You're always very good at keeping your mouth shut.
真对不起 不要了
- You know what? Hey,I'm so sorry,forget it.
这 这是新的标准程序了吗?
Is this--Is this the new standard procedure?
大白天的玩骚扰?
Harassment in broad daylight?
一年后 我还是会在查的
- A year from now,I'm still gonna be looking.
只要一个闪失 哪怕是给你的奶奶 一个股票消息 我就会抓住你 小子
One slip,so much as give your grandma a stock tip,I'm gonna get you,kid.
证监会就是一群没牙的看门狗
- The s.E.C. Is a watchdog without teeth.
连停车罚单也开不了
You couldn't give a parking ticket.
还好我在司法部有朋友
- Good thing I got friends in the justice department.
他们就爱送有钱的白人去劳教所
They love sending rich white boys up to otisville.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
Carter把证监会的密封文件送来了
- Carter sent over the sealed s.E.C. Files.
去年 Doug Rasmussen调查员 追查了Baylor Zimm的内线交易指控
Inspector doug rasmussen pursued possible counts of insider trading at baylor zimm last year.
质询针对的是高层主管
The inquiry was aimed at top tier executives.
Adam是被传唤的证人 但所有指控都撤销了
Adam was a subpoenaed witness,but all charges were dropped.
他作证说 公司上层管理者没有任何错误做法
He testified to knowing of zero wrongdoing among the upper management of the firm.
我相信他撒了谎 来保护他的老板 Sydney Baylor
I believe he was lying to protect his boss,sydney baylor.
Adam现在在干什么?
What's adam up to now?
直奔皇后区去了
- Headed all the way out to queens.
他似乎有胆量挑衅一个做餐车生意的人
Looks like he's got a bone to pick With a guy in a food truck.
嘿 兄弟
- Hey,buddy.
上个礼拜 我从你这流动厕所里 买了个德国小香肠吃
I had a bratwurst from this rolling outhouse last week,hit me worse than a master cleanse.
比清肠药还厉害 我要打电话到卫生部举报
I'm calling the department of health,okay?
有什么问题
- You know,i don't see what the problem is,
因为现在你可以把你那副 柔弱的内脏塞回你的二千块的西服里去了
'Cause now you can stuff that soft gut of yours back into your $2,000 suit.
三千块的西服
- $3,000 suit.
三千? 一套西服?
- $3,000? For a suit?
三千块买套西服 你好啊 兄弟?
$3,000 for a suit. How are you,pal?
好
- Good.
餐车是Robert Sowoski的
- The food truck is registered to robert sowoski.
那个法定监护人?
- The legal guardian?
怎么 你不再回老家转转了?
What,you don't come around The old neighborhood anymore?
忙啊 Bob舅舅
Life in the fast lane,uncle bob.
进来 我给你弄点吃的
Come on in. I'll get you something to eat.
他不单单是法定监护人 他还是Baylor Zimm的客户
- He's more than a guardian,he's also a baylor zimm client.
我问过的MNP你看了吗?
- Hey. Did you look into that m.N.P. I asked about?
MLP: 公开上市交易的有限合伙企业
-  m.L.P,uncle bob. "Master limited partnership."
是MLP Bob舅舅 意思是 "业主有限责任合伙企业"
而你这家是 Tritak能源
And it's called tritak energy.
Tritak 对 对
- Tritak,right. Right.
听着 我知道你跟你办公室那些 算钱的打过招呼 让他们照顾好我的钱了
Look,I know you told those fancy number crunchers Over at your office to take care of my money,
但是我在读那些他们发给我的资料
But I'm reading all this material they keep sending me.
好像有太多钱都流向这一个公司了
It looks like an awful lot of cash going into one company.
我就老是看见 "Tritak Tritak"
I mean,I keep seeing it. "Tritak. Tritak."
以前是10% 现在变40
I mean,it was 10%,now it's 40.
即便是我这种投资白痴 也知道要分散投资 对吗?
Even a financial dunce like myself knows You got to diversify,right?
Bob舅舅 我会教错你吗?
- Uncle bob,would I steer you wrong?
谁帮你减税?
Who got you those tax breaks?
谁帮你找的低息贷款?
Who got you that low-Interest loan?
- 你以前只有一辆货车 现在 - 现在我有六辆
You had one truck,now-- - Now I got six trucks.
20个伙计
20 employees.
还有据我所知 回报率是8%
- And from what I heard,that m.L.P. Is returning 8%.
上哪儿还能找这么高的回报率?
Where else are you gonna find that kind of return on your money?
相信我给你找的投资经纪
Trust that broker that I set you up with.
- Adam... 我信你 - 啊?
- Adam...i do. - What?
你是天才 你一直都是
- You're a genius,and you always have been.
谢谢
- Thank you.
我们都知道Tritak能源些什么 Finch?
What do we know about tritak energy,finch?
知道得不多 跟紧Adam
- Not much. Stay close to adam.
看看你能查出点什么
See what you can find out.
顺带一提 Saunders给我找了个态度很好 的经纪 高兴地我们的钱给了Baylor Zimm
On a side note,saunders guided me to a very kind broker who happily deposited our money in baylor zimm.
希望你记得拿收据 Finch
- Hope you got a receipt,finch.
Saunders先生 我们预约了 我来最好敲定那笔投资
Mr. Saunders,we had an appointment to finalize that deposit.
给我一分钟
- Uh,give me-- Give me one minute.
嗨 Paul?
Hey,paul?
Paul 你有时间吗?
Paul,you got a sec?
嗯
- Yeah.
那公司 我上礼拜问过的能源公司Tritak?
- That company-- That energy company I asked you about last week,tritak?
你昨天在一世纪里最大的做空上 赚了一亿 然后今天就来问MLP?
- You made $100 million yesterday in the short of the century and you're asking about some m.L.P.?
- 谁在乎啊? - 那是我舅舅的钱 我在乎
Who cares? - It's my uncle's cash. I care.
所有固定收入客户都扔去买MLP了
- All the fixed -Income crowd is getting dumped into m.L.P.S.
稳健又无聊
It's safe,boring.
这不光是我舅舅 公司一半的客户也在买
- It's not just my uncle,it's half the clients at this firm,and it's half the firm.
我上礼拜查过了
I ran the numbers last week.
Baylor Zimm 19%的交易都在这玩意上
Baylor zimm is invested in this thing to 19%.
有人留意过这事吗?
Anybody even tracking that?
你查了客户的钱?
- You've been looking into client money?
你不能这么做 知道吧?
You know you can't do that,right?
联邦法律说你不能
Like,federally you can't.
这是非法的... 连我和你谈都是非法的
It's illegal... and so is this conversation.
谢谢你提醒
- Thanks for the tip.
嘿 不然朋友是干啥的?
- Hey,what are friends for?
- 我们晚点再谈 - 好
We'll talk later. - Yeah.
我听说今天证监会找你问话了怎么回事?
- What's this i hear about you getting questioned by the s.E.C. Today?
没事 还是那个Rasmussen 新一天问老问题
- It's nothing. It's the same guy,rasmussen.New day,same song.
别管他 我有事要找你
He's got nothing.But I need to talk to you.
你还记得有天晚上我问你那公司 Tritak?
You remember that company i asked you about the other night,Tritak?
不如我们把晚上谈的事留在晚上?
- How about we keep what we talk about at night,at night?
还有证监会 记住上次我们只是侥幸过关
And as for the s.E.C.,just remember the last time we barely got off the hook.
我们熬不过另一桩丑闻
We can't take another embarrassment.
你是说公司受不了另一桩丑闻 对吗?
- You mean the firm can't take another embarrassment,right?
低调行事 Adam 拜托啦
- Keep your head down,adam. Please.
我要放松的时候就来这里
- I come here a lot when I need to decompress.
让我心灵平静
It's peaceful.
你今天在办公室跟人争什么?
- So what were you argui about at the office today?
你的客户不需要担心的事
- That isn't anything that your client needs to worry about.
是证监会吗  这种我的客户显然要担心的事?
- Is the s.E.C. Something my client needs to be worried about?
这行有些人总想耍手段玩花样
- In this business,someone's always trying to find the trick,the con.
是啊 那你呢?
- Right. So what's yours?
我们就是懂行而已
- We're just that good.
所以你才把你舅舅的钱也投到公司里?
Is that why you invested your uncle's money with the firm?
什么?
- Excuse me?
我们投了一亿五千万
- We have $150 million on the line.
当然什么都想知道 Adam
We'd like to know everything,adam.
你姓"Saunders"对吧?
"Saunders" is your given name,right?
但"Sowoski"不是更好吗?
But wouldn't "sowoski" be more accurate?
你找人跟踪我?
- Are you having me followed?
好吧 我们走
All right,let's go.
我载你回公司 如果他们还想要你的钱 总会有其他蠢货愿意接手
I'm driving you back to b.Z.,And if they still want your money,some other schmuck can handle it.
我们说清楚了 我的家人 我的过去 与你无关 不管你投了多少钱
So we're clear,my family,my past is none of your business,No matter how much money is at stake.
好吧
- Right.
也许我应该报警
- You know,maybe I should call the police.
- 也许你是要报警 - 你说什么?
- You may need to. - What are you talking about?
你看到那边的建筑工地了吗?
- You see the construction equipment back there?
嗯 我看见了 怎么了?
- Yeah,I see it. So what?
你看见有工人吗?
- You see any workers with it?
你什么意思 他们让我减速
- What do you mean? They want me to slow down.
我们被逼进绝境了 别停车!
- We're being funneled. Don't stop!
有人想除掉Adam Finch
Someone just tried to kill adam,finch.
昨晚之后Saunders先生还好吗?
- How's mr. Saunders after last night?
他以为是一场意外
- He thinks it was an accident.
你确定不是?
- And you're sure it wasn't?
我们被逼进绝境了
- It's called "funneling."
巧妙地诱使目标驶入绝境
You force your target into a kill zone by subtly shifting his direction.
Carter在现场调查
Carter's looking at the scene now.
那辆车 还有停车标志
The vehicles,the stop light.
职业杀手干的 可谁这么想Adam死 还请了职业杀手?
It was professional,but who wants adam dead enough to bring in a hit team?
我在监控我的钱
- I've been watching my money.
大部分都投进了一家公司的股票
The majority of it is being shuffled into one company--
Tritak Adam的舅舅也提过
Tritak,same one that adam's uncle mentioned--
只不过是他的十倍
Only at ten times the rate that his money was invested.
有人的动作更迅速了
Someone is moving faster than before.
Tritak投资了路易斯安那州/德州 往东北部的输气管道
- Tritak invests in the louisiana/texas pipeline running gas to the northeast.
人们需要天然气
- People need natural gas,
大致来说 Tritak的股价应该稳定
So for the most part,tritak should keep a steady price,
但由Baylor Zimm掀起的疯买 使股价最近涨了600%
But it shot up 600% recently because of a buy frenzy initiated at baylor zimm.
- 内线交易? - 以前发生过
- Insider trading? - Happened before.
Adam那时知道情况 也许现在也知道
Adam knew about it then,maybe he knows about it now.
不过他这次可没法脱身了
- Except he won't walk away this time.
昨晚差点在路上被杀
We were almost roadkill last night.
我不高兴再兜圈子了
I'm getting tired of playing around.
Sowoski先生 我是证监会的
- Mr. Sowoski,I'm with the s.E.C.
我们在调查Bylor Zimm投资 有没有违法行为
We're looking into possible criminal activities at baylor zimm investments.
你的侄子是那儿的交易员
We know your nephew is a trader there.
什么? 他违法了?
- What? Did he do something wrong?
我们也不知道
- We can't be sure.
Adam有没有给你理财建议?
Does adam advise you on your own investments?
没有 我有经纪人的
- No,I got a broker for that.
那你知不知道...
- What can you tell me about...
Tritak能源公司?
a company called tritak energy?
不太清楚 这得问我经纪人
- Not much. You'd have to talk to my guy.
但你投了很多钱进去 对吗?
- But your own money is heavily invested in it,correct?
对
- Yeah.
我知道那件事有点古怪
You know,I knew there was something fishy going on there,
但是Adam 他给我介绍的经纪人好
But adam,he put me with good people.
他说没问题的
He said it was fine.
你对你侄子有多了解?
- How well do you know your nephew?
我姐姐死后 Adam的爸爸去西部谋差
- When my sister died,adam's dad left to find work out west.
他最后在新墨西哥州定居 再也没回来
He ended up in new mexico. He never came back.
所以Adam跟我们住一起
So adam lived with my family.
每个月 他父亲寄来200块 买漫画书 新鞋子都可以
Every month,his father sent $200 home,for whatever,comic books,new shoes.
Adam从来没用过
Adam never spent it.
一年又一年 他把所有的钱存在鞋盒里
Year after year,he saved every penny in shoe boxes.
有好几千块
It was thousands.
长大以后 他用这笔钱读夜校 直到考上了真正的商校
And when he grew up,he used it to enroll in night classes before he could get into a real business school.
所以 尽管Adam没有父亲...
And in the end,what adam had instead of a father was...
他存了一盒钱
cash in a shoe box.
他拿来干嘛了? 他买到了美好的前途
And what did he do? He bought himself a future.
Saunders 我们得谈谈 现在
- Saunders,we should talk,now.
关于Tritak
Tritak.
一个平庸的公司最近 突然变成市场上最枪手股票
A run-Of-The-Mill m.L.P. Just happens to be the hottest damn equity on the market these days.
你知道些什么情况
You tell me what you know.
我什么都不知道
- I don't know anything.
我想等你进了劳教所 你就记得了
- Oh,I'll bet you'll start remembering when you're up in otisville.
不过到那时候 可没得商量了
But by then,it'll be too late to make a deal.
好吧 好吧
- Okay. Okay.
好吧 听着
All right,look. Look.
那天晚上 我计算了些数据
I ran some numbers the other night.
似乎... 不大对头
It looks like-- It doesn't add up.
找不出Baylor Zimm 巨额投资这家公司的原因
There's no reason why Baylor zimm should be dumping so much money into this one company.
除非... 除非有人知道 我们不知道的底细
unless--Unless somebody knows something the rest of us don't.
你的数据还在吗?
- You still have the numbers you ran?
在我办公室手提电脑里
- On a laptop,in my office.
去拿
- Get it.
马上
Now.
借过
- Excuse me.
Reese先生 出事了
- Mr. Reese,we have a problem.
他在屋顶
He's on the roof.
我们得离开这儿 快
- We got to get you out of here. Come on.
快点
We have to move fast.
这栋楼不安全
This building is tactically unsafe.
你不是资产经理
- You're not an asset manager.
不是 但我能救你的命
- No,but I did save your life.
到底发生了什么事?
- What the hell happened back there?
有人第二次企图谋杀你
- Just a second attempt to kill you.
我要知道Tritak让人不断那么做的原因
I need to know what about tritak has people repeatedly trying to do that.
是从我舅舅开始的
- I--It started with my uncle.
单位把他的钱投资到一个公司
The firm invested him in a company.
他问了我一些情况 所以我去偷偷查了下
He asked me some questions,so I took a peek.
这违法的?
- Illegally?
对 但他是家里人 我没想这么多
- Yeah,but he was family. I didn't think anything of it.
但我看到一些数据 有问题
And then I saw some numbers that I didn't agree with,
所以我写了个邮件 准备发给 风险管理人 律师 合伙人 所有人
So I wrote an email. I was going to send it to risk management,legal,the partners,everybody,
后来... 证监会开始暗中调查 他们要我不要乱说
But then--Then the s.E.C. Started sneaking around,so I was told to keep my mouth shut.
你觉得是内线交易?
- You think it was insider trading?
这不是第一次了  但我没把邮件发出去
- It wouldn't be the first time,but look,i never sent that email.
你告诉别人了吗?
- Did you tell anyone else?
公司里几个朋友
- A few friends at the firm.
我... 我让他们留意一下...
I--I asked them just to take a look at it,and--
谁?
Who?
Sydney Baylor
- Sydney baylor.
拿到你要的调查结果了 Carter
- I got the search results that you wanted,carter.
近几周只有一个公用设施地 报告车辆失窃
Only one utility yard reports vehicle thefts in the last week.
都在3天前被盗
- All stolen three nights ago.
挖掘机 压路机和刚翻新的环卫车?
Back hoe,steam roller,and a refurbished sanitation vehicle?
要旧的垃圾车干什么?
What would somebody want with an old garbage truck?
谢谢
Thanks.
Reese先生 找到Sydney Baylor吗?
Mr. Reese,did you find sydney baylor?
嗯 现在在她公寓 可她说不了什么了
Yeah,we're at her penthouse now,but she isn't saying much.
追杀Adam的人 先杀了她
Whoever is after adam got to her first.
是我的错
- This is my fault.
我问了她 关于Tritak数据的事
I asked her about the tritak numbers.
她肯定自己去查了
She must have looked into them herself.
上帝 他们杀了她
Oh--Oh,my god. They killed her.
Adam 你认得这个酒瓶吗?
- Adam,you recognize that bottle?
嗯 那天晚上为庆祝 做空维尔塔南的股票喝的
- Yeah,we drank it the other night To celebrate the virtanen short.
那就是说 到处有你的指纹
- Which means your fingerprints are all over it.
到处都有
Everywhere.
Finch Baylor因为调查了 自己公司的底细被杀了
Finch,they killed baylor for digging into her own company.
害死Adam之前 伪造成他干的
Made it look like adam did it before plunging to his own death.
警察来了 该撤了
The cavalry's here. Time to go.
警察会到处找Adam
The police will be all over adam.
你准备怎么办?
What are you going to do with him?
带他去安全的地方 走
- I'll take him somewhere safe. Come on.
死因是头部钝挫伤
- Cause of death was blunt force trauma to the head.
- 指纹? - 找到两个
- Prints? - I dusted twice.
浴缸和身上都没有
None on the tub,none on the body.
只找到受害人和Adam Saunders的指纹
Only other ones we found were the vic's and an adam saunders.
我们认为他和受害人是恋人关系
We think he was having a relationship with the victim.
家里和凶器上都有他的指纹
His prints are all over the home and murder weapon.
你是说那个香槟酒瓶?
- You mean the champagne bottle?
你怎么知道的?
- How'd you know that?
-  这里 - 谢了
- Here. - Thanks.
有没有可能Saunders和受害人 的确是恋人关系
Is there any chance,if saunders was having a relationship With the vic,
所以几天前他摸过香槟酒瓶 然后被人栽赃?
that he could have handled the champagne bottle,Say,days ago,then had it planted?
那就狡猾了
- That'd be pretty slick.
但谁会搞这么麻烦呢?
But who'd go through the trouble?
在公寓楼的大垃圾箱里翻个遍?
You'd have to,what,search the building's garbage?
地下室是进不去的
Anyway,basement's guarded.
除非他们有垃圾车
-  unless they had a garbage truck.
Reese先生 咱们在市里 有不少安全地点能安置Adam
Mr. Reese,we have many safe houses in the city where adam could be taken.
我知道
- I know.
没人知道我是谁的时候最安全
The safest I've ever been was when I was anonymous.
给 你也很安全
Here. You'll be safe,too.
等等 你不能把我丢这儿
- Wait,you can't leave me here.
我不能在这儿睡
I can't sleep here.
为什么不能? 我就睡过
- Why not? I did.
就在那儿 睡了4个月
Right over there,for four months.
看到那个女人吗? 她叫Joan
See that woman? Her name is joan.
如果有什么需要 问她
If you need anything,just ask her.
呃 就是别碰她车里的东西
Oh,uh,just don't touch anything in her cart.
给
Here.
除非我打给你 不要用这个电话
Don't use this phone until I call you on it.
等等 等等
- Wait,wait,wait.
Victor 去找Victor
Victor,go find victor.
夜店的朋友?
- Your pal from the nightclub?
他是高级经纪人
- He's the senior broker.
如果有人要为Tritak拉客户 不管愿不愿意
If someone's putting clients in tritak,whether or not they want it,
接下来能拿到回扣的就是他
He's the next rung down on the brokerage ladder.
如果这一议案今天没通过 就会被无限期搁置
if this bill had not been passed today,It would have been put aside indefinitely,
而这对纽约州是不利的
Which we feel would be detrimental to the state of new york.
有麻烦了 Reese先生
- We have a problem,mr. Reese.
出什么事了?
- What else is new?
你听说过尤蒂卡的页岩 或水力压裂技术吗?
- Have you heard about utica shale or the process of fracking?
呃 是地下岩层
- It's,um,underground rock formations.
那些公司挖开页岩床释放天然气
- Companies dig down and fracture shale beds to release natural gas.
刚通过的议案批准了 纽约北部的挖掘工作
They just passed a bill to start fracking in upstate new york,
意味着他们不需要 南部来的输气管了
Which means they wouldn't need a pipeline up from the south.
也不用投资Tritak这样的公司了
- And they don't need to invest in a company like tritak.
Baylor Zimm向Tritak投了多少钱?
How much did baylor zimm have invested in tritak?
或他的客户投了多少钱?
Or how much did its clients?
上百万
- Millions.
成千上万 他们会倾家荡产
Millions upon millions,and they will lose everything.
Adam预见这一情况 企图阻止
Adam saw this coming,tried to stop it.
所以他们要杀他
- Which is why they tried to kill him.
但他们是谁?
- But who are they?
Adam叫我去找Victor
- Adam told me to talk to victor.
说他应该知道
Said he would have to know.
议案昨晚通过了
- The bill passed overnight.
我尽快卖掉你的股票
I'm trying to sell your shares as fast as I can.
你个软柿子
You're a patsy.
他们利用了你
They just used you,
但你的老板死了 Adam命悬一线 成千上万人倾家荡产
But your boss is dead,adam's life is on the line,and millions were lost.
人们需要那个钱 他们有家庭
People needed that money. Families.
我以为压Tritak是安全的
- I thought tritak was a safe bet.
有人买通参议员 有很有权的人 足以推动页岩开采议案通过
Someone got to the senators,someone powerful enough to push that shale fracking bill through the system.
为什么抬高Tritak的股价?
- But why build tritak up?
为什么要做掉Adam...
Why silence adam...
就是为了看它破产吗?
only to watch it fail?
Tritak能源暴跌
Tritak ***out
这是清仓
Listen,it's a short sale.
有人操纵交易员抬高价格高价卖出
Someone had the brokers pump up the price and then sold high,
因为他们知道法案会通过 会毁了Tritak
Because they knew that the bill was gonna pass and kill tritak.
这时做空的人能赚几百万
Whoever shorted it stands to make millions on this.
所以他们才盯上你
- That's why they targeted you.
那我们怎么把做空的人找出来?
So how do we find the short-Seller?
看看你周围 几十个交易员都在卖Tritak
- Look around you--There's 50 brokers selling off tritak.
我们要找几天前就卖了的那些人
We need to find the guys who already sold it days ago,
因为现在他们为了掩饰要买回来
Because now they have to cover the short and buy it back.
我得挂了
I got to go.
嗨 Bob舅舅
Hey,uncle bob.
Adam 怎么了? 你告诉我Tritak很可靠
- Adam,what's going on? You told me tritak was safe.
Bob 对不起 非常抱歉 我会把你的钱拿回来
- Bob,I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'll get your money back.
那不是仅仅是我的钱 Adam
- It's not just my money,adam.
那是大家的工资和养老金
It--It's salaries. It's pensions.
我手下所有人的钱都在那儿
It's every employee that works for me.
那是我的生意 写着Sowoski这个名字
It's my business,the sowoski name.
Bob 我
- Bob,i-I-- Look--
你不姓Sowoski 至少你自己不这么想
- But you're not a sowoski,at least you never thought you were.
你姓Saunders
You're a saunders.
不是么 Adam?
Isn't that right,adam?
不是的 听着 我会把钱拿回来--
- No,listen-- Listen,I'll get it back.
哪怕花上我下半辈子我也要拿回来
Even if it takes the rest of my life,i will get it back.
我得挂了
I got to go.
嗨 老大?
- Hey,boss?
我想我找到那小子了
I think I got a location on the kid.
我要你帮忙 Finch.
- I'm going to need your help on this,finch.
我要你混进Baylor Zimm
I need you to get inside baylor zimm.
我在交易层了
- I'm on the trading floor now.
Reese先生 我找到了点东西
Mr. Reese,i found something.
Paul Ashton
Paul ashton.
Adam的朋友
- Adam's friend.
同时也是高级风险管理经理
- Also a senior risk manager.
我发现他上周下了做空的单
I found his short-Sale orders from last week,
今早开始买进
And the buy orders for tritak,issued to him this morning.
多少?
- For how many?
大概四百万
- About $4 million.
Paul现在在哪里?
- Where is paul now?
我正要找出来
- I'm about to find out.
他的电话和日程表相连  我也许能查到他的位置
His phone is tethered to his calendar. Maybe I can hack into his gps.
- Paul? 不可能
- Paul? It can't be.
不 我说不可能
No,i-I mean,really,it can't.
交易诈骗受到严格监管
They put measures in place to catch securities fraud,
包括内部交易 操纵做空等等 Paul怎么办到的?
Insider trading,short-Sale manipulation,how did paul do it?
Paul不是单独行动
- Paul isn't working alone.
他在证监会有内应
He's got a friend in the s.E.C.
我职业生涯都在调查非法交易 到头来反倒是我的部门被削弱
- I spent my entire career chasing down rogue traders,only to see my agency get defanged
正在最需要我们紧密调查的时候被削弱
When the country needed us watching the closest.
真可悲
Pity.
斗不过就同流合污呗
You can't beat 'em,you join 'em.
顺便赚个几百万
- And make millions along the way.
准确来说是三亿 情况如何?
- 300 million,to be exact. Where are we?
Tritak今天收市跌到4块一股了
- Tritak was down to $4 a share by closing bell today.
明天一开市就变两块
When the market opens tomorrow,it'll be $2.
我已经准备好买进我们需要的量了
I've got buy orders in place to pick up the shares that we need.
那漏网之鱼呢?
- And the loose ends?
Baylor不会问问题了 但Adam还在外面
- Well,baylor won't be asking any more questions,but adam is still out there.
他可能是个后患
He could be a problem.
我会解决他
- I have it under control.
你最好团好那纸团塞到你衣服下面
You'd be better off balling up that paper and stuffing it under your clothes.
这样能保暖
It'll keep you warm.
我怎么落到这境地?
- See,how did-- How did it get to this?
我说...
I mean...
我所获一切都是努力挣来的
i earned everything that I achieved in my life.
我知道
- I know.
- 你舅舅告诉我了 - 你和他谈过了?
Your uncle told us. - You talked to him?
他说了你爸爸的事  还有他寄来的200块
- He told us about your father and the $200 he'd send you.
他不知道这故事的结局
- He doesn't know the end of the story.
他不知道我16岁时去找我爸爸
He doesn't know when I was 16,i went to go find my father.
我坐火车去新墨西哥城 找到了他...
I took a train to new mexico,and I found him...
他已经有了新家庭
and he had a-A new family.
我找到他之后 他打算再给200块打发我
And then when I went to him,he tried to hand me another $200.
我不要那些钱
I didn't want the money.
我要一个家
I wanted a family.
你找到了...
- And you found one...
你舅舅一辈子辛辛苦苦窝在餐车里 赚钱供你
an uncle who spent his life slaving over a food-Truck counter...for you.
我会把Bod的钱拿回来 我答应他了
- I'll get bob's money back. I promised him that I would.
你什么时候和你舅舅说过话?
- When did you talk to your uncle?
趴下!
- Get down!
你在干什么? 我们得走! 现在就走!
- What are you doing? We need to go! We need to move!
蹲好
- Stay down.
现在可以走了
Now move.
这么说Paul一直和Rasmussen暗中勾结?
- So paul was working with rasmussen all along?
合伙大量做空Tritak
- On a massive short -Sell bet against tritak.
已经减值90%了
It's lost 90% of its value already.
但证监会调查员和银行家都不会用 自动武器扫射流浪汉的营地
But an s.E.C. Investigator and a banker do not shoot up a homeless encampment with automatic weapons.
不会 幕后还有老道的打手
- No. There was some serious muscle behind this.
Adam怎么样了?
- How's adam doing?
对一个什么都没有了的人来说还不错
- Not bad for a guy who's lost everything.
他还有西装吗?
- Does he still have a suit?
- 怎么了?  - Paul和Rasmussen 要Tritak先触底他们才能进账
- Why? - Paul and rasmussen need tritak to bottom out before they can collect on their bet.
什么意思 Finch?
- What are you talking about,finch?
尝试去接过一把下落的刀吗 Reese先生?
- Ever try to catch a falling knife,mr. Reese?
想弄伤手这主意倒不错
- Sounds like a good way to get cut.
所以我们需要一位极其在行的投行家
- Which is why we need a damn good investment banker.
叫Adam打好领带 他要重返职场了
Have adam put on a tie. He's going back to work.
Tritak 我要1000手Tritak
- Tritak,i need 1,000 units of tritak.
我要买 我要买进Tritak
I need to buy. I got to buy on tritak.
搞什么鬼?
- What the hell?
Victor 我要你帮忙
Victor,i need your help.
我接到买4百万Tritak的单
I've got buy orders here for 4 million shares of tritak.
你能马上买进么?
Can you fill these immediately?
市场上有我就能买
- Uh,I can buy what's available,
但今天有新玩家大量买进
But some new player hit the market hard today--
持续一早上了
Been buying all morning.
倒是能买好多手 我说 你过来看看?
There's a lot out there to buy. I mean,would you look?
Tritak涨到15元一手了
Tritak just hit 15 a unit.
等到后知后觉的外行反应过来 它肯定已经到史上最高点了
By the time the dumb money gets back in,it'll be at an all-Time high.
- 新玩家是谁? - 匿名的
- Who's the new player? - Anonymous.
但我有号码
But I have a number.
也许你能谈成一笔
Maybe you can strike a deal.
你找我什么事?
- Hey,you called. What's going on?
我在救咱们的命! 还问什么事
- I'm saving our asses. That's what's going on.
我是Harold Crane 有何贵干?
- This is harold crane. Yes?
先生 我是Baylor Zimm投资的 Paul Ashton
- Sir,this is paul ashton with baylor zimm investments.
我想和你谈谈你大量持有的 Traitak能源股
I need to speak with you about your majority share in tritak energy.
抱歉 这你得和我的投行家谈
- I'm sorry. You'll need to speak to my banker about that.
等等 先生
- No,sir! I--
抱歉 Paul 但我小小地买进这么一下 重新拉高了Tritak的股价
- Sorry,paul,but my little buying frenzy just reinvigorated the tritak m.L.P.,
而我手上握着绝大部分
And I own all the shares.
别担心 我会把你要的卖你
Don't worry. I'll sell you what you need.
说到底 朋友不就是这样么?
After all,what are friends for?
你那个"掩饰做空"的小伎俩...
Your little game of "hide the short"...
不犯法的情况下才行得通
only works when it's legal.
你没有证据
- You can't prove anything.
我没有 但Victor 还有其他交易员会排队指证你
- No,I can't,but victor and a dozen other brokers just lining up to testify against you--
只要不用坐牢 他们什么都愿意
They'll do anything to avoid jail time.
让开 就是那个人
- Let us through here. That's the guy.
过来
Over here.
那里! 拦下他!
There! Get him!
John Rooney 资产经理
- John rooney,assets.
你的钱 一分不少
- It's all of it,all your money.
我小时候只信赖你
You were the only person that i counted on when I was younger,
我希望你也能信赖我 希望有天你原谅我
And I wish that you could have counted on me,and I hope that someday maybe you can forgive me.
我当然原谅你了 孩子
- Of course i forgive you,kid.
我们是一家人
You're family.
没事 我原谅你...
Of course I forgive you...
虽然我不能苟同你选西装的品味
even if I can't and your taste in suits.
我再问问你 接下来投资什么呢?
- So let me ask you this-- What are we gonna do about reinvesting?
我想也许我们可以扩展生意
- I think that maybe you and I could look Into franchising the business,
但首先有些人我们得先喂饱
But first I got some people i want you to feed.
认识你以前我不知道你干哪行 John
I didn't know what you were into before we met,john,and
我现在也不知道  但你这日子过得可一点都不无聊
I don't know now,but...you sure know how to keep things interesting.
我看到楼下贴了告示
- I saw signs posted downstairs.
终于有人买了这破地方
Someone finally bought this old place.
"新业主"
- "New ownership."
看来我们要到别的地方去了
It looks like we'll have to make camp elsewhere.
事实上...
- Actually...
我认识新业主
i know the new owner.
他是个聪明小子...
He's a smart kid...
心肠也不赖
with a good head on his shoulders.
我想你不用搬了
I don't think you'll have to be moving anywhere.
我从来没说谢谢你
i never said thank you...
谢谢你在我需要的时候照顾我
for looking after me when I needed it.
现在是谁在照顾你?
- Who's looking after you these days?
一个新朋友
- Someone new.
大银行家哈?
- Some big -Shot broker,huh?
另外那个呢?
- Where's the other one?
哪个?
- What other one?
应该有两个嫌犯
- There are supposed to be two suspects.
- 你说证监会那人? - 嗯
- You talking about the s.E.C. Guy? - Yeah.
他们在他皇后区的寓所找到了他的尸体
- They found him dead in his apartment in queens--
一枪崩了自己的脑袋
Self-Inflicted g.S.W. To the head.
大概是受不了要蹲大牢吧
Guess he couldn't stand the thought of otisville.
我听说他们一起被捕的
I heard they both were arrested.
我不知道怎么跟你说
- I don't know what to tell you.
我在想...
- I was thinking...
这一切都太干净利落了 太复杂了
all of this was all too slick,too complicated.
股票经纪人和证监会调查员干不来
A stockbroker and a finance cop couldn't pull this off.
幕后还有人
No,there was someone else behind the scenes,
雇了一队杀手
Someone who hired a team of assassins,
在法案通过前几星期就知道
Who knew a bill would pass in state government weeks before it did,
这人能动用三亿来开战
Someone who could use $300 million to finance a personal war.
这是什么?
- So what's this?
更大的阴谋
- The bigger picture.
你好 John
- Hello,john.
好久不见
It's been a long time.
《疑犯追踪》 第1季 第16集
Person of Interest S01E16 720p HDTV x264
-= 伊甸园字幕 =-